- Raj, that's incredible.
- Congratulations.
Excuse me, 30 what under 30 what
to watch what?
(Raj:)Thirty visionaries
under 30 years of age to watch...
(Raj:)...as they challenge
the preconceptions of the fields.
(Sheldon:)If I had a million guesses,
I never would have gotten that.
They've got me in with a guy doing
something about hunger in Indonesia...
...a psychotherapist using dolphins
to rehabilitate prisoners...
(Raj:)...and Ellen Page,
star of the charming independent film Juno.
(Howard:)Oh, I'd so do her.
(Leonard:)You'd do the dolphins.
Do I get a mention...
(Howard:)...for designing the telescope camera
mounting bracket?
(Raj:)Sorry, it's not part of my heartwarming
and personal narrative...
(Raj:)...in which a humble boy
from New Delhi...
(Raj:)...overcame poverty and prejudice and
journeyed to America to reach for the stars.
Poverty? Your father's a gynecologist.
He drives a Bentley.
(Raj:)It's a lease.